<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>
	<MidSaverSaver.Settings.DisableCompression>Fix hash collisions</MidSaverSaver.Settings.DisableCompression>
	<MidSaverSaver.Settings.DisableCompression.Desc>If you encounter a hash collision after adding a mod, you may notice problems such as:\n\n\n1.) Stone cliffs or chunks have disappeared, or have transformed into a different item.\n\n2.)The deep drill is turning up unusual items.\n\nTo use this fix correctly, you must enable it *before* you add the new mod, then save your game with it enabled. This creates a save without any compression (lossy compression is the source of this problem). Then you can add the mod, and you're free disable this setting or disable this mod entirely.</MidSaverSaver.Settings.DisableCompression.Desc>
	
	<MidSaverSaver.Settings.FixCorruptWorldObjects>Fix faction removal</MidSaverSaver.Settings.FixCorruptWorldObjects>
	<MidSaverSaver.Settings.FixCorruptWorldObjects.Desc>If you remove a faction, you may be unable to view the world map, or load any new saves created after you removed the factions. To use this fix:\n\n\n1.) Enable it and load your save with the faction mod(s) removed. You will get many red errors, but ignore them.\n\n2.) Open the world map, and the console should mention something about corrupt world objects being removed by Mid-Saver Saver.\n\n3.) Save your game.\n\n4.) Check if you can load your save. If you can, you're good to go and should disable this fix, or even the mod entirely.</MidSaverSaver.Settings.FixCorruptWorldObjects.Desc>
	
	<MidSaverSaver.Settings.FixCorruptSectors>Fix corrupt areas and sections</MidSaverSaver.Settings.FixCorruptSectors>
	<MidSaverSaver.Settings.FixCorruptSectors.Desc>If you remove a mod that had custom coded areas or section layers, it could corrupt the map's managers for these components. When this happens you'll get a "grey screen of death" on loading a save. This fix will regenerate them:\n\n\n1.) Enable it and load your save with the mod(s) removed. You will get many red errors, but ignore them.\n\n2.) Save your game.\n\n4.) Check if you can load your save. If you can, you're good to go and should disable this fix, or even the mod entirely. If your areas were corrupted, you'll need to build these yourself (the home area, roofing areas, snow clear areas, etc).</MidSaverSaver.Settings.FixCorruptSectors.Desc>
</LanguageData>